Contact

midhat.fatima21@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/midhat-f-b5b852126 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Selenium JMeter RubyMine

Midhat Fatima

Test Engineer | Automation | SQA Pakistan

Summary

3+ years of experience in testing Desktop/Web/Mobile Applications, and APIs in both Windows and Linux environments.

Hands-on experience in Automation frameworks (Selenium and .Net/Java, Ruby Capybara, Jmeter, K6.io, Javascript, NUnit, TestNG, BDD Cucumber). Experience with Version Control systems like Git. Solid understanding and practical experience of software development life cycle (SDLC).

Experience working with Agile and Waterfall software development methodologies. Work in close

collaboration with QA, Engineering, Product, Business teams to create test strategies.

Eager to quickly learn new technologies, tools and methods. Team player with can-do approach. Great work ethic focused on business success.

Experience

Systems Limited
Senior QA Automation Engineer
July 2021 - Present (9 months)
Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

10Pearls

Test Engineer Automation November 2019 - June 2021 (1 year 8 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

- 1- Functional test Automation of website using Ruby Capybara and cucumber.
- 2- Performance testing of AWS AppSync GraphQL APIs.
- 3- Manual, GUI, Regression, Smoke and E2E testing.
- 4- Test case writing, Test Planning, release notes.
- 5- Bug Reporting, Story Analysis, and Task tracking by utilizing Jira.

TPS Worldwide

Test Automation Engineer|Selenium|CICD|DevOps

Page 1 of 2

March 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 8 months)

Karachi

- 1- E2E test Automation of website using VisualStudio and Nunit framework.
- 2- Extent Reporting, Excel and Database Integration and manipulation.
- 3- Performance and Back end testing of APIs using Jmeter.
- 4- Data Driven Testing, Security testing automation script writing.
- 5- TFS Build pipeline for Automation projects.

KCompute (Pvt) Ltd.
Web Developer
November 2017 - February 2018 (4 months)
Karachi

Worked as Php WebDeveloper

KayGeeS (Kazmi Global Systems)
Web developer internee
September 2017 - October 2017 (2 months)
karachi

JASB Group SAP ABAP Trainee April 2016 - August 2016 (5 months) Karachi Pakistan

Education

Karachi University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Computer Science · (2013 - 2016)